Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand!
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day?
And the values we had were about to
collapse Oh just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone.
We'll go where we all wanna go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
To be
continued...
Hurry, this way! Yeah!
Damn, we're trapped here.
You're right.
The heat will kill us before we get out.
Yes, this is it!
You're Jinbei from the
Straw Hats! Thank you!
You're really strong!
Head the opposite way.
The fire hasn't spread there yet.
Just focus on surviving.
All right.
We'll save ourselves.
You stay safe too! Right! Now go!
Yeah!
You heard the man!
Why did the flames spread so quickly?
It's one thing for a
warrior to die in battle,
but this fire will cause so
many needless casualties!
It's too dangerous to stay here now.
We need to run to some place safer.
Is something wrong, Doctor?
Fighting for a nation!
She's back!
Yay!
Oh, Doctor!
I'm so glad!
And as an added bonus,
now you, Karoo, know the side effects
of your extended gigantification.
Yeah, I thought something might
happen, but I didn't expect that.
It's a fair payoff.
I'm stronger and bigger for longer,
but weaker and smaller once it's over.
But that reminds me there's someone
else dealing with side effects.
Miyagi, I'm worried
about how Zoro's doing.
Indeed, it won't be pretty.
He had 20 or 30 bones broken and had
countless other injuries on top of that.
The medicine healed him instantly,
but doesn't last forever.
When it's done, he'll hurt twice as bad?
Yeah.
Those wounds were bad
enough in the first place.
Zoro, you better not die.
Who the hell are you?
What do you want?
Hey, no, what the hell's
going on, I can't,
I can't move, stay back, don't do it, no!
Out of my way!
I ain't got time for this crap!
I gotta find Zoro!
This isn't fair.
We had this till one of
Whitemir's commanders stepped in.
Why the hell is he hoping
Straw Hat and the Samurai?
I'm a sloppy.
The peace pirates aren't
to be trifled with.
Kaku, keep him up.
It's fine.
As long as you're safe.
Cypher-pull.
Indeed, we're Aegis Zero.
I was afraid this might happen.
Izo, we never saw each other.
To be clear, the Whitebeard pilots
committed a historical crime.
That's not something we can simply ignore.
But our business is with the Straw Hats,
and that is more than enough for now.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
We are not done here.
CP Zero.
Just a little more.
I can still make it!
Don't you dare!
Wearing all hands.
And slips into the rain.
Don't do that! Come on!
What is your deal?
Namuji!
Place your fight!
If that thing so much as touches those
explosives, everything will be over.
I don't know where you came
from, but you can go right back!
Mahoropa!
That's enough, Big Mom! Please!
They can't even move anymore!
You've won, okay?
You don't have to kill them!
Come on!
I'm begging you!
Even your own men are pitying you.
It's not a good look for
the worst generation.
Hey, hurry up! Hmm?
They want this by us!
Just run out a little
longer and we'll save you!
I need any medics to move in and
take care of the captain right now!
No!
Screw off, you punks!
This is a proper duel!
And we're not done!
God of lightning, Timton, heed my call!
Whoa!
Straight into the rubbish
pile, right where you belong.
Nom, nom, nom, nom!
You know, it's funny.
I thought Kaido would have
announced his victory by now.
Don't tell me he's still
fooling around with Straw Hat.
Put that brat in the ground already.
He's just a little punk.
Kara, let's go to the rooftop.
Yes, Mama.
Sounds like fun.
I'm pooped after all this.
Now let's get the hell out of here.
Mama, Mama, Mama.
Turning your back on the enemy?
K-Room.
It's time for anesthesia.
You're finished, Straw Hat!
Mama!
I think it just killed Big Mom! Mama!
Oh, wow.
Didn't know Drop could do that.
I know I hurt you with this last time,
but the incision isn't the point.
This is...
No, let's not be hasty.
Chakvila!
Oh, my God!
Ah!
How dare you!
Huh?
Something's pulling me!
You're steel beams, right?
You don't need to talk.
You're all working for me now.
You still got some vibes. Not bad.
You must really want my head,
you stubborn little brass.
Come on.
I did want your head,
but all of a sudden I feel I'm
being driven by a different purpose.
I have a feeling Kaido's
end is coming soon, too.
Even raindrops can wear away stone
if you give them long enough.
You think you're invincible?
There's no such thing!
You just haven't faced
anyone persistent enough!
Baaahhh! PUNK!
Turn TOO!
What the hell is that thing?
She's super-sized and
it's bigger than her!
Hey!
Listen up, you old nasty hag!
We're gonna drive you straight to hell!
You're not!
Get in on that road!
It's working!
Onigashima is moving backward!
I'll drag it as far away
from the capital as possible!
You will not harm my people!
You will not reach the land of
Wano so long as I draw breath!
Did someone call out to me?
That thing just sent her flying!
Big Mub's not actually
going to lose this, is she?
I finally got you to shut up for
a second hey you you did it again
that's two times now I did a powerful
move and you followed my lead with
something big and flashy acting
like you one get your ego in check
because i'm not your opening act my
ego nobody here gives a crap except you
all right then why don't you attack
her first next time anybody's
strongest technique didn't let me
finish her off now screw that you're not
my boss besides the next move i do
is gonna wipe her out with or without
you oh yeah what comes after the
bull a hippo an elephant SHUT UP!
I AIN'T GONNA TELL YOU CRAP!
Oh, jeez.
Watch your mouth, Law, or the
boss is gonna kill you next.
Hey, look!
Shock waves inside my body.
Oh my ribs must be broken.
That's quite the dangerous technique.
Hear that?
Even she thinks it's cool.
Real funny.
Now will you drop it already?
You dick.
A life force should fix things.
Now, Bones, come to life!
Yes, Mama!
This is serious, so listen.
I've only got enough left
in me for one more attack.
We've got to finish
this with the next shot.
I don't intend to lose.
So what I need you to do...
I just said you're not my boss!
I don't want to hear it!
Prometheus!
Napoleon!
Hera!
Let's go! Ready, Mama?
I could do this all day!
Masira Saber!
It's just scraps!
You're wasting your time!
This was always a waste of time.
You were dead the moment
you picked this fight.
I've sunk hundreds of boats like you.
I was ruling when you
were still in diapers.
My power is absolute best for me.
to be an emperor of the sea.
Now a side!
Ah!
Huh?
Yen!
Hold on, what are you?
What is this?
Papa, get away!
I'm stuck!
She used the tower to block it?
Why don't you take a head drop dead?
Stupid brat.
You must learn your place.
Mother's visit. Cannon!
Three thousand leagues of misery!
What the hell is that thing?
You can't escape me!
Our attack is chasing us down.
It's alive!
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma!
Time to finish them all!
Put those little punks
in the ground, Misery!
Now tucked!
K-Room.
This trick I can't revolve her!
Is that a sword?
You'll pay for that.
You've got some balls on you!
How long did you sit
here to hold on to me?
Captain, no!
What are you doing, Captain?
Let go! You're gonna die!
It's not worth it!
Deeper. Deeper.
Just a little more.
This is pointless.
You really wanted me to
beat you to death, huh?
Now puncture.
Huh?
What are you doing? Fall!
What's going on?
A giant hole?
Where did that come from?
What are they doing up there?
Burn him to ash, Misery!
Eustass! Do it already!
What's that?
Telling me what to do again, Trafalgar!
Just sit there and keep your mouth shut!
You're gonna ship me!
I'm not scared of you, you nasty boy.
Give me your worst.
You can't beat Big Mom.
Keep telling yourself that.
Now jump. Mom!
You don't rule in our era.
Your time sucks.
You pulled out all the stops this time.
Honestly, I'm impressed.
You boys must really like me.
You don't want our time together to end,
even though you can
barely stand on your feet.
You're young, of course,
and you've got lots of energy, but I'm
made of much sterner stuff than you.
You flats probably thought
you'd driven me to the brink,
but try as you might, you can't defeat me!
She's not dead?
What the hell is it gonna take?
They've been kicking her ass, but
now she's just laughing at all.
Come on, boss!
This is insane!
Kid and the captain are both spent.
We're screwed!
And when I do, your miserable little
life will be putty in my hands.
I'll grant you what mercy.
You may choose your punishment.
Would you like to hand over
50 years of your lifespan?
Or would you rather stay
as you are and be my slave?
Will it be life or slave?
You took so much ass!
That's enough, boss!
We gotta book it!
It's not fair!
She's taking her life pants too!
Stop it! Hi, boy! Hi, boy!
No!
Don't say anything but this!
I thought she was going to die,
then she turns around and does this!
She's a monster!
You've got to run!
Get away from here, Captain!
You guys should run.
What a joke.
She thinks I'm scared.
Now I'm not giving you a damn thing.
And I'll never be your slave.
This is just a bluff.
You've got one foot in
the grave, you old hag,
and your half-assed threats
don't intimidate me!
I can't believe it!
Not even a second of their
lifespan has been taken away!
She's an emperor on the sea!
You're telling me they're
not scared at all?
Roronoa.
As much as I'd like to relish my victory,
the dying screams will probably ruin it.
Unless I do this.
A gift from the man who saved me.
Stop being such a sore loser
and take a hit, damn it!
The Underworld is waiting!
Let me help you on your way! It's silence!
Huh?
Is something wrong with my ears?
Scream into the void.
We've heard enough.
This technique cancels out all sound.
Sorry, didn't catch that.
What's happening?
My voice is gone!
Captain, look behind you!
And one more for the road!
Jack!
Prometheus!
Hera!
Anna!
What are you doing?
Why aren't you helping me?
What?
That big mom!
What happened?
Everything's silent!
Nothing I touch makes the sound!
What the hell have you done
to me, Trafalder? Whoa!
Let it go!
It's gone!
What?
Is that smoke?
What's going on?
Curse those stupid brats!
And curse you too, Roger!
You just couldn't keep your mouth shut!
Why the hell did you have to go
and say that before you died?
So you all want my treasure?
Well, you can go ahead and have it.
It's out there.
I left it in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
People ain't bad up.
The whole world bought into it.
Great pirate era but what do you care
you're dead it's not your problem is it?
All these brats got fired up
thanks to your little speech Roger!
And the pirates you left behind from your
generation we're the ones
who have to deal with them.
That doesn't sound good!
We need to leave now!
Is there anyone there?
What was that noise?
Someone answer me!
Otter!
It's not fair, Otter.
You should have told us
before you left this world.
The One Piece.
Is the treasure even real?
What is it?
Where is it?
It could be right beneath my
nose and I wouldn't have a clue.
It's so frustrating!
Kid!
Look!
You won't get away with this.
My story isn't over.
It can't be.
Not like this, dammit.
I won't die.
Not from this!
Mark my words, I will be back!
The battle between Emperor of the Sea
Big Mom and the New Generation has ended.
On the performance floor inside the skull
dome a cheer rings out
the winners are clear
After a desperate struggle
Eustass captain kid
And his ally the surgeon of death
Trafalgar Law are victorious at last.
You did it, boss!
Captain!
You beat a new prophecy!
This is a big deal!
A really big deal!
I see.
So it's you.
But why have you come?
All right.
This will do for now, at least.
Wow!
I knew you could do it,
Momonosuke! Keep it up!
Yamato, it's you!
Is that the basement? Oh no!
It's exposed!
It's been a real mess.
Big Mom just set off a bomb.
It blew out half the wall.
I saw the explosion earlier.
So that was her doing, was it?
Uh-huh.
I'm lucky the whole armory didn't explode.
I was able to freeze everything,
so we should be safe for now.
That's good news.
I'm glad to see that you are unharmed.
I'm still fighting to do my part,
but I need to tell you something.
We have a very large visitor coming.
Are you familiar with
Zunesha the giant elephant
the same one Odin wrote
about in his journal?
Impossible. Papa!
Zunesha was a companion of Joy Boy
who committed a crime 800 years ago.
What could it all mean?